const data = [

    {
        question: "Children, at what time are you going ... school today?",
        incorrectAnswers: [
            "at",
            "to the",
            "at the"
        ],
        correctAnswer: "to"
    },

    {
        question: "She has been waiting for her boyfriend ... October",
        incorrectAnswers: [
            "for",
            "already",
            "from"
        ],
        correctAnswer: "since"
    },

    {
        question: "We haven't got ... money to buy a new car yet",
        incorrectAnswers: [
            "too many",
            "too much",
            "enough"
        ],
        correctAnswer: "enough"
    },

    {
        question: "The little girl had a cup of tea in ... hands",
        incorrectAnswers: [
            "his",
            "your",
            "the"
        ],
        correctAnswer: "her"
    },

    {
        question: "How old is your brother, Susan? He ... ten yesterday",
        incorrectAnswers: [
            "is",
            "has",
            "had"
        ],
        correctAnswer: "was"
    },

    {
        question: "How ... are you going to be in Madrid, Mr. Smith?",
        incorrectAnswers: [
            "much",
            "time",
            "many"
        ],
        correctAnswer: "long"
    },

    {
        question: "There ... children in the park, weren't there?",
        incorrectAnswers: [
            "was a lot",
            "were a lot",
            "was lots of"
        ],
        correctAnswer: "were a lot"
    },

    {
        question: "You can speak Swedish better than your uncle, ...?",
        incorrectAnswers: [
            "can you",
            "don't you",
            "speak you"
        ],
        correctAnswer: "can't you"
    },

    {
        question: "That old lady drinks too much, ...?",
        incorrectAnswers: [
            "does she",
            "isn't it",
            "drinks she"
        ],
        correctAnswer: "doesn't she"
    },

    {
        question: "How ... are you going to give Martha for her work",
        incorrectAnswers: [
            "-",
            "many",
            "money"
        ],
        correctAnswer: "much"
    },


]

export default data;